

Krisztina Vancsa

Small Art business owner-Teacher

CONTACTS

+40747425270

kriszty.xx@gmail.com

IG: @flowergirlwithahat

CAREER OBJECTIVE

An Artist who tries to navigate in the world, with lots of real life experiences in a ''paper matter'' world. Also, a compassionate teacher with 10 years of working experience with children. Skilled at introducing new technologies into classrooms for optimized student interest. Committed to closely monitoring progress for long-term success with child-centric teaching methods.

With photography and creative writing skills.

EMPLOYMENT

Freelance artist/designer 2018 -present

- Drawings and paintings.
- Pattern and logo designs.
- Decorations. Cards.
- Art shop owner
- Creative ideas for children

Private teacher/Teacher - 06/2020-06/2022

- Teaching English and Art with child centric methods. Differentiated instruction according to student ability and skill level.
- Helped students build learning and study skills to achieve educational goals.
- Taught students in various stages of cognitive, linguistic, social and emotional development
- Built and strengthened positive relationships with students and parents. Worked one-on-one with students to create individualized lesson plans to increase progress

Digital Marketing Executive 05/2019-08/2019 - Delhi, India

- Searching potential clients in European field
- Building and development of international sales.
- Coordination and processing international exhibition stand and design projects.
- Interfaced with clients to discuss budget allocation to determine project scope.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Art: Liberal Art and Finnish language University of Debrecen 2015

- o Studying philosophy.
- o Writing.
- o Film.
- o Finnish language.
- o Art History.
- o Religion.

Master of Arts: Aesthetic and Art Theory University of Debrecen 2017

- o Writing.
- o Art history.
- o Philosophy.
- o Film.
- o Analysis.
- o Essay writing.

Languages

Mother tongue: Hungarian Fluent: in English Romania Latin

EMPLOYMENT

Assistant teacher - 12/2017 - 12/2018 - Delhi, India - IB curriculum

- Teaching art classes, play activities and organizing classes
- Drama classes, helped with stage, decoration.
- Facilitate English and creative writing classes during the school summer camp.
- Substitution classes in 1-4 grades
- Took care of the school resources (organizing and distribute).
- Summer camp activities.
- Contributed to positive, educational setting by delivering gentle discipline and promoting student success.
- Fulfilled multiple duties, including tutoring basic skills, and grading homework and exams.

Volunteer 12/2015 - 06/2016

- Worked in a hospital with kids and perform daily childcare activities
- Assist organized family and children based activities, mostly art and craft.
- Teaching and helping to children with learning disabilities and unprivileged background

Summer Camp stuff (06/2014 - 08/2015 USA)

- Worked with children as well.
- Took care of them, organized activities and played with them.
- Engaged campers in creative games and sports-related activities to encourage participation and healthy competition.

SUMMARY OF skills

- Strong creative vision
- Excellent classroom management
- Creative lesson plan development
- Flexible scheduling
- Organizational strengths
- Positive atmosphere promotion

Strategic planning

Motivating students

Adaptable

Creative and artistic

Quick learner

Analytical thinker